Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Jean Mayer, administrative records and related papers, 1939 -- 2006; 1976 -- 1992; UA001.013; 45.6 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Subject files, 1939 -- 1996; UA001.013.001
    - Vannevar Bush professorship, 1975 -- 1977; UA001.013.027.00001 (Box 27)
    - Vannevar Bush professorship, 1974 -- 1978; UA001.013.027.00002 (Box 27)
    - Venture Program, 1973 -- 1976; UA001.013.027.00003 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School, 1978 -- 1980; UA001.013.027.00004 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School, 1986 -- 1987; UA001.013.027.00005 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School, 1988; UA001.013.027.00006 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School, 1989 -- 1990; UA001.013.027.00007 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.013.027.00008 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: miscellaneous, n.d., UA001.013.027.00009 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: miscellaneous, 1980 -- 1984; UA001.013.027.00010 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: miscellaneous, 1981; UA001.013.027.00011 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: accreditations, 1981 -- 1984; UA001.013.027.00012 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: accreditations site visit, 1983; UA001.013.027.00013 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: accreditations site visit, 1983; UA001.013.027.00014 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: accreditation report, 1979; UA001.013.027.00015 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: admission, 1980 -- 1984; UA001.013.027.00016 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: budget, 1980 -- 1983; UA001.013.027.00017 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: budget, 1979 -- 1980; UA001.013.027.00018 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: contracts, 1977 -- 1985; UA001.013.027.00019 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: dean search, Dean Jonas, 1977 -- 1978; UA001.013.027.00020 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: dean search, 1981; UA001.013.027.00021 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: faculty, 1980 -- 1982; UA001.013.027.00022 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: federal, 1986 -- 1987; UA001.013.027.00023 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: fundraising, 1978 -- 1980; UA001.013.027.00024 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: fundraising #2, 1981 -- 1983; UA001.013.027.00025 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: fundraising #3, 1979 -- 1984; UA001.013.027.00026 (Box 27)
    - Veterinary School: government, 1980 -- 1987; UA001.013.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: Grafton, 1978 -- 1983; UA001.013.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: MSPCA, 1981 -- 1985; UA001.013.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: MSPCA, 1979 -- 1981; UA001.013.028.00004 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: personnel, 1979 -- 1983; UA001.013.028.00005 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: possible students, 1976; UA001.013.028.00006 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: reports, 1976 -- 1985; UA001.013.028.00007 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: supporters (individuals), 1976; UA001.013.028.00008 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: supporters (corporations), UA001.013.028.00009 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: supporters (government officials), 1975 -- 1976; UA001.013.028.00010 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: supporters (veterinary clubs, sportsman, etc.), 1976; UA001.013.028.00011 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: tuition, 1980 -- 1985; UA001.013.028.00012 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: visiting committees/3-year plan, n.d., UA001.013.028.00013 (Box 28)
    - Veterinary School: visiting committees/3-year plan, n.d., UA001.013.028.00014 (Box 28)
    - WGBH Educational Foundation, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.013.029.00001 (Box 29)
    - Watkins/Doe, 1991; UA001.013.029.00002 (Box 29)
    - Wessell-Hall/Hoag Collection, 1986; UA001.013.029.00003 (Box 29)
    - White House Conference on Health and Nutrition, 1989 -- 1990; UA001.013.029.00004 (Box 29)
    - White House Conference on Health and Nutrition, 1987 -- 1989; UA001.013.029.00005 (Box 29)
    - Wildenstein, 1979 -- 1986; UA001.013.029.00006 (Box 29)
    - Women, 1977 -- 1981; UA001.013.029.00007 (Box 29)
    - People and Plows Against Hunger: Self-help experiment in a rural community, 1975; UA001.013.039.00001 (Box 39)
      Foreword by Jean Mayer
      Black, Herbert
    - Famine: A symposium dealing with nutrition and relief operations in times of disaster, 1971; UA001.013.039.00002 (Box 39)
      Blix, Gunnar; Hofvander, Ynge; Vahlquist, Bo
    - Fairbank Remembered, 1992; UA001.013.039.00003 (Box 39)
      Mayer writes briefly on page 48
      Cohen, Paul; Goldman, Merle
    - Lasting Slimness: Physical Fitness, 1967; UA001.013.039.00004 (Box 39)
      Forward by Jean Mayer
      Collins, Corrine
    - Foreign Affairs, 1974; UA001.013.039.00005 (Box 39)
      Article by Jean Mayer page 98.
      Council on Foreign Relations
    - Jacques Et Therese Trefouel, 1980; UA001.013.039.00006 (Box 39)
      Signature from author on first page. This publication written in French.
      Courrier, Robert
    - The Challenge of Famine Recent Experience: Lessons Learned, 1993; UA001.013.039.00007 (Box 39)
      Field, John Osgood
    - Calorie Requirements, 1957; UA001.013.039.00008 (Box 39)
      Food and Agriculture Organization
    - Proceedings 50th Anniversary Symposium of the the Food and Nutrition Board, 1990; UA001.013.039.00009 (Box 39)
      Food and Nutrition Board; Institute of Medicine
    - Making Decisions, 1978; UA001.013.039.00010 (Box 39)
      Foreword by Jean Mayer.
    - Eater's Digest: The Consumer's Factbook of Food Additives, 1976; UA001.013.039.00011 (Box 39)
      Jacobson, Michael
    - The Greatest Adventure: Basic Research That Shapes Our Lives, 1974; UA001.013.039.00012 (Box 39)
      Kone, Eugene; Jordan, Helene
    - Hunger In America: The Federal Response, 1979; UA001.013.039.00013 (Box 39)
      Kotz, Nick
    - Let Them Eat Promises: The Politics of Hunger in America, 1969; UA001.013.039.00014 (Box 39)
      Note and signature from author on first page of the book.
    - Health, 1974; UA001.013.039.00015 (Box 39)
      Mayer, Jean
    - Diet & Nutrition Guide: Sound, Reliable Advice from America's Most Respected Nutritionist, 1990; UA001.013.039.00016 (Box 39)
      Mayer, Jean; Goldberg, Jeanne
    - Overweight, 1969; UA001.013.039.00017 (Box 39)
    - World Nutrition: A U.S. View, 1978; UA001.013.039.00018 (Box 39)
    - U.S. Nutrition Policies in the Seventies, 1973; UA001.013.039.00019 (Box 39)
    - Some Aspects of the Problem of Regulating Food Intake and Obesity, 1970; UA001.013.039.00020 (Box 39)
      Reprinted from the International Psychiatry Clinics journal.
    - 31 Days To A Slimmer You!, 1975; UA001.013.039.00021 (Box 39)
    - Fats, Diet & Your Heart, 1976; UA001.013.039.00022 (Box 39)
    - What To Look For On A Label, 1976; UA001.013.039.00023 (Box 39)
    - Protein: How Much Is Enough, 1975; UA001.013.039.00024 (Box 39)
    - Nutrition and Civilization, 1967; UA001.013.039.00025 (Box 39)
      Reprinted from Transactions of the New York Academy of Sciences
    - Andre Mayer, Scientist, Soldier, Statesman, 1956; UA001.013.039.00026 (Box 39)
      Reprinted from the SCIENCE journal.
    - Hunger and Undernutrition in the United States, 1990; UA001.013.039.00027 (Box 39)
      Reprinted from the Journal of Nutrition
    - Genetic, Traumatic and Environmental Factors in the Etiology of Obesity, 1953; UA001.013.039.00028 (Box 39)
      Reprinted from the Physiological Reviews
    - Terminologie De L'Alimentation Et De La Nutrition, 1969; UA001.013.039.00029 (Box 39)
      This publication is printed in French.
      Mayer, Jean; Akroyd, W.R.
    - Recommended Dietary Allowances, 1974; UA001.013.039.00030 (Box 39)
      National Research Council
    - The New England Conference on Food, Nutrition & Health Final Report Volume I: Findings and Recommendations, 1979; UA001.013.039.00031 (Box 39)
      New England Conference on Food, Nutrition & Health
    - Health for Life, 1987; UA001.013.039.00032 (Box 39)
      Richmond, Julius; Pounds, Elenore; Corbin, Charles
    - Harvard's Department of Nutrition 1942-86, 1987; UA001.013.039.00033 (Box 39)
      Stare, Fredrick J.
    - Forum: For Applied Research and Public Policy, 1992; UA001.013.040.00001 (Box 40)
      Article by Jean Mayer.
      The University of Tennessee Energy, Environment, and Resourc; Oak Ridge National Laboratory
    - Sustaining Tomorrow, 1984; UA001.013.040.00002 (Box 40)
      Article by Jean Mayer in this publication.
      Thibodeau, Francis; Field, Hermann
    - Family Health, 1971; UA001.013.040.00003 (Box 40)
      Family Health Magazine
    - Hunger In America: Chronology and Selected Background Materials, 1968; UA001.013.040.00004 (Box 40)
      United States Senate
    - Overcoming World Hunger: The Challenge Ahead, 1980; UA001.013.040.00005 (Box 40)
      United States Presidential Commission on World Hunger
    - Panel Recommendations to the White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health, 1969; UA001.013.040.00006 (Box 40)
      United States White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and
    - Preliminary Views of the Voluntary Action Task Forces to the Provisional Draft of Panel Recommendations to the White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health, 1969; UA001.013.040.00007 (Box 40)
    - Hunger USA, 1968; UA001.013.040.00008 (Box 40)
      Citizens Board of Inquiry in Hunger and Malnutrition in the
    - Hunger USA Revisited, 1970; UA001.013.040.00009 (Box 40)
    - Food: Readings from Scientific American, 1973; UA001.013.040.00010 (Box 40)
      Article by Jean Mayer on page 21.
    - Heart Facts, 1979; UA001.013.040.00011 (Box 40)
      American Heart Association
    - Obesity and Health, 1970; UA001.013.040.00012 (Box 40)
      U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    - Scientific American, 1976; UA001.013.040.00013 (Box 40)
      Article by Jean Mayer on page 40.
      Scientific American, inc.
    - Modern Medicine, 1973; UA001.013.040.00014 (Box 40)
      Jean Mayer is on the cover and has an article in this publication.
      Modern Medicine
    - Food Engineering, 1974; UA001.013.040.00015 (Box 40)
      Jean Mayer is on the cover and is interviewed in this publication.
      Chilton
    - Snack Food, 1970; UA001.013.040.00016 (Box 40)
      American Trade Publishing Company
    - World Monitor, 1988; UA001.013.040.00017 (Box 40)
      Christian Science Monitor
    - The World, 1989; UA001.013.040.00018 (Box 40)
      Unitarian Universalist Association
    - Current Biography, 1970; UA001.013.040.00019 (Box 40)
      Biography of Jean Mayer on page 27.
      H.W. Wilson Company
    - Index Biographique des membres des associes et des correspondants De L'Academie De Medecine, 1991; UA001.013.040.00020 (Box 40)
      Biography of Jean Mayer on page 142. This publication is in French.
      Academie De Medecine
    - Research Publications of the Department of Nutrition Harvard School of Public Health 1942-1975, 1976; UA001.013.040.00021 (Box 40)
      Presented to Jean Mayer for his inauguration as Tufts Univerisity president.
      Harvard University
    - Insights and Issues in Nutrition, 1977; UA001.013.040.00022 (Box 40)
      This publication are presentations presented at the Martha F. Trulson Memorial Lectures.
      American Dietetic Association
    - Reader's Digest, 1974; UA001.013.040.00023 (Box 40)
      Article on page 159 references Jean Mayer.
      Reader's Digest Association
    - Baccalaureate Address, 1986; UA001.013.040.00024 (Box 40)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1974; UA001.013.040.00025 (Box 40)
    - Untitled Draft, 1974; UA001.013.040.00026 (Box 40)
    - The Dimensions of Hunger: Who is Hungry, and Why? Scientific American article draft, 1976; UA001.013.040.00027 (Box 40)
    - Book proposal, 1983; UA001.013.040.00028 (Box 40)
    - Chapter outline, 1974; UA001.013.040.00029 (Box 40)
      Draft of chapter 2 from the book Health.
    - Draft chapter on exercise for book on nutrition, 1983; UA001.013.040.00030 (Box 40)
    - The End of Mealtimes, 1972; UA001.013.040.00031 (Box 40)
      Article published in Family Health.
    - 10 Nutritional Myths, 1979; UA001.013.040.00032 (Box 40)
    - Micro Colorimetry, 1970; UA001.013.040.00033 (Box 40)
    - Publications and Correspondence, 1967 -- 1973; UA001.013.040.00034 (Box 40)
    - Testimony on behalf of Consortium for Prototype Health Sciences Information Systems, 1984; UA001.013.040.00035 (Box 40)
    - Drafts and Proposals, 1975 -- 1982; UA001.013.040.00036 (Box 40)
    - Mayer list of publications, 1965; UA001.013.040.00037 (Box 40)
    - Congressional record and correspondence, 1992; UA001.013.040.00038 (Box 40)
    - White House Conference, 1969; UA001.013.040.00039 (Box 40)
    - Mayer articles, 1955 -- 1969; UA001.013.040.00040 (Box 40)
    - Newspaper articles, 1969 -- 1993; UA001.013.040.00041 (Box 40)
    - Tufts inaugural address, 1976; UA001.013.040.00042 (Box 40)
    - Bangladesh Sahel, 1974; UA001.013.040.00043 (Box 40)
      This folder contains a UNICEF News publication
    - Government recommendations, 1974; UA001.013.040.00044 (Box 40)
    - The Regulation of Hunger and Appetite, 1955; UA001.013.040.00045 (Box 40)
      Academy of Sciences
    - Research photographs, 1955 -- 1980; UA001.013.040.00046 (Box 40)
  - Food for Thought newspaper column, 1972 -- 1993; UA001.013.002
    This group contains copies of the Food for Thought newspaper column and it is arranged chronologically.
    - March-June, 1972; UA001.013.041.00001 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00002 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00003 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00004 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00005 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00006 (Box 41)
    - July, 1972; UA001.013.041.00007 (Box 41)
    - August, 1972; UA001.013.041.00008 (Box 41)
    - August, 1972; UA001.013.041.00009 (Box 41)
    - August, 1972; UA001.013.041.00010 (Box 41)
    - August, 1972; UA001.013.041.00011 (Box 41)
    - September, 1972; UA001.013.041.00012 (Box 41)
    - September, 1972; UA001.013.041.00013 (Box 41)
    - September, 1972; UA001.013.041.00014 (Box 41)
    - September, 1972; UA001.013.041.00015 (Box 41)
    - September-October, 1972; UA001.013.041.00016 (Box 41)
    - October, 1972; UA001.013.041.00017 (Box 41)
    - October, 1972; UA001.013.041.00018 (Box 41)
    - November, 1972; UA001.013.041.00019 (Box 41)
    - November, 1972; UA001.013.041.00020 (Box 41)
    - November, 1972; UA001.013.041.00021 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00022 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00023 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00024 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00025 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00026 (Box 41)
    - December, 1972; UA001.013.041.00027 (Box 41)
    - 1973, UA001.013.041.00028 (Box 41)
    - 1973, UA001.013.041.00029 (Box 41)
    - January, 1973; UA001.013.041.00030 (Box 41)
    - January, 1973; UA001.013.041.00031 (Box 41)
    - January, 1973; UA001.013.041.00032 (Box 41)
    - January, 1973; UA001.013.041.00033 (Box 41)
    - January, 1973; UA001.013.041.00034 (Box 41)
    - January-March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00035 (Box 41)
    - February, 1973; UA001.013.041.00036 (Box 41)
    - February, 1973; UA001.013.041.00037 (Box 41)
    - February, 1973; UA001.013.041.00038 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00039 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00040 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00041 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00042 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00043 (Box 41)
    - March, 1973; UA001.013.041.00044 (Box 41)
    - April, 1973; UA001.013.041.00045 (Box 41)
    - April, 1973; UA001.013.041.00046 (Box 41)
    - April, 1973; UA001.013.041.00047 (Box 41)
    - April, 1973; UA001.013.041.00048 (Box 41)
    - April, 1973; UA001.013.041.00049 (Box 41)
    - April-May, 1973; UA001.013.041.00050 (Box 41)
    - May, 1973; UA001.013.041.00051 (Box 41)
    - May, 1973; UA001.013.041.00052 (Box 41)
    - May, 1973; UA001.013.041.00053 (Box 41)
    - May, 1973; UA001.013.041.00054 (Box 41)
    - May-June, 1973; UA001.013.041.00055 (Box 41)
    - May-July, 1973; UA001.013.041.00056 (Box 41)
    - June, 1973; UA001.013.041.00058 (Box 41)
    - June, 1973; UA001.013.041.00059 (Box 41)
    - June, 1973; UA001.013.041.00060 (Box 41)
    - June-July, 1973; UA001.013.041.00061 (Box 41)
    - June-August, 1973; UA001.013.041.00062 (Box 41)
    - July, 1973; UA001.013.041.00063 (Box 41)
    - July-August, 1973; UA001.013.041.00064 (Box 41)
    - July-August, 1973; UA001.013.041.00065 (Box 41)
    - August, 1973; UA001.013.041.00066 (Box 41)
    - August-September, 1973; UA001.013.041.00067 (Box 41)
    - August-September, 1973; UA001.013.041.00068 (Box 41)
    - August1973-June 1980, UA001.013.041.00069 (Box 41)
    - September, 1973; UA001.013.041.00070 (Box 41)
    - October, 1973; UA001.013.041.00071 (Box 41)
    - October, 1973; UA001.013.041.00072 (Box 41)
    - October, 1973; UA001.013.041.00073 (Box 41)
    - October, 1973; UA001.013.041.00074 (Box 41)
    - November, 1973; UA001.013.041.00075 (Box 41)
    - November, 1973; UA001.013.041.00076 (Box 41)
    - November, 1973; UA001.013.041.00077 (Box 41)
    - November, 1973; UA001.013.041.00078 (Box 41)
    - November, 1973; UA001.013.041.00079 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00080 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00081 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00082 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00083 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00084 (Box 41)
    - December, 1973; UA001.013.041.00085 (Box 41)
    - December 1973-January 1974, 1973 -- 1974; UA001.013.041.00086 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00087 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00088 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00089 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00090 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00091 (Box 41)
    - January, 1974; UA001.013.041.00092 (Box 41)
    - February, 1974; UA001.013.041.00093 (Box 41)
    - February, 1974; UA001.013.041.00094 (Box 41)
    - February, 1974; UA001.013.041.00095 (Box 41)
    - February, 1974; UA001.013.041.00096 (Box 41)
    - February, 1974; UA001.013.041.00097 (Box 41)
    - March, 1974; UA001.013.041.00098 (Box 41)
    - March, 1974; UA001.013.041.00099 (Box 41)
    - March, 1974; UA001.013.041.00100 (Box 41)
    - March-April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00101 (Box 41)
    - April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00102 (Box 41)
    - April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00103 (Box 41)
    - April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00104 (Box 41)
    - April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00105 (Box 41)
    - April, 1974; UA001.013.041.00106 (Box 41)
    - April-May, 1974; UA001.013.041.00107 (Box 41)
    - May, 1974; UA001.013.041.00108 (Box 41)
    - May, 1974; UA001.013.041.00109 (Box 41)
    - May, 1974; UA001.013.041.00110 (Box 41)
    - May, 1974; UA001.013.041.00111 (Box 41)
    - June, 1974; UA001.013.041.00112 (Box 41)
    - June, 1974; UA001.013.041.00113 (Box 41)
    - June, 1974; UA001.013.041.00114 (Box 41)
    - June, 1974; UA001.013.041.00115 (Box 41)
    - June, 1974; UA001.013.041.00116 (Box 41)
    - June 1974, September 1991, 1974 -- 1991; UA001.013.041.00117 (Box 41)
    - July, 1974; UA001.013.041.00118 (Box 41)
    - July, 1974; UA001.013.041.00119 (Box 41)
    - July, 1974; UA001.013.041.00120 (Box 41)
    - July, 1974; UA001.013.041.00121 (Box 41)
    - August, 1974; UA001.013.041.00122 (Box 41)
    - August, 1974; UA001.013.041.00123 (Box 41)
    - August, 1974; UA001.013.041.00124 (Box 41)
    - August, 1974; UA001.013.041.00125 (Box 41)
    - September, 1974; UA001.013.041.00126 (Box 41)
    - September, 1974; UA001.013.041.00127 (Box 41)
    - September, 1974; UA001.013.041.00128 (Box 41)
    - September, 1974; UA001.013.041.00129 (Box 41)
    - September, 1974; UA001.013.041.00130 (Box 41)
    - October, 1974; UA001.013.041.00131 (Box 41)
    - October, 1974; UA001.013.041.00132 (Box 41)
    - October, 1974; UA001.013.041.00133 (Box 41)
    - October, 1974; UA001.013.041.00134 (Box 41)
    - November, 1974; UA001.013.041.00135 (Box 41)
    - November, 1974; UA001.013.041.00136 (Box 41)
    - November, 1974; UA001.013.041.00137 (Box 41)
    - November, 1974; UA001.013.041.00138 (Box 41)
    - November-December, 1974; UA001.013.041.00139 (Box 41)
    - December, 1974; UA001.013.041.00140 (Box 41)
    - December, 1974; UA001.013.041.00141 (Box 41)
    - December, 1974; UA001.013.041.00142 (Box 41)
    - December, 1974; UA001.013.041.00143a (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00143b (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00144 (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00145 (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00146 (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00147 (Box 41)
    - January, 1975; UA001.013.041.00148 (Box 41)
    - February, 1975; UA001.013.041.00149 (Box 41)
    - February, 1975; UA001.013.041.00150 (Box 41)
    - February, 1975; UA001.013.041.00151 (Box 41)
    - March, 1975; UA001.013.041.00152 (Box 41)
    - March, 1975; UA001.013.041.00153 (Box 41)
    - March, 1975; UA001.013.041.00154 (Box 41)
    - March, 1975; UA001.013.041.00155 (Box 41)
    - March, 1975; UA001.013.041.00156 (Box 41)
    - April, 1975; UA001.013.041.00157 (Box 41)
    - April, 1975; UA001.013.041.00158 (Box 41)
    - April, 1975; UA001.013.041.00159 (Box 41)
    - April, 1975; UA001.013.041.00160 (Box 41)
    - May, 1975; UA001.013.041.00161 (Box 41)
    - May, 1975; UA001.013.041.00162 (Box 41)
    - May, 1975; UA001.013.041.00163 (Box 41)
    - May, 1975; UA001.013.041.00164 (Box 41)
    - May, 1975; UA001.013.041.00165 (Box 41)
    - June, 1975; UA001.013.041.00166 (Box 41)
    - June, 1975; UA001.013.041.00167 (Box 41)
    - June, 1975; UA001.013.041.00168 (Box 41)
    - June, 1975; UA001.013.041.00169 (Box 41)
    - June, 1975; UA001.013.041.00170 (Box 41)
    - July, 1975; UA001.013.041.00171 (Box 41)
    - July, 1975; UA001.013.041.00172 (Box 41)
    - July, 1975; UA001.013.041.00173 (Box 41)
    - July, 1975; UA001.013.041.00174 (Box 41)
    - July, 1975; UA001.013.041.00175 (Box 41)
    - August, 1975; UA001.013.042.00001 (Box 42)
    - August, 1975; UA001.013.042.00002 (Box 42)
    - August, 1975; UA001.013.042.00003 (Box 42)
    - August, 1975; UA001.013.042.00004 (Box 42)
    - August, 1975; UA001.013.042.00005 (Box 42)
    - September, 1975; UA001.013.042.00006 (Box 42)
    - September, 1975; UA001.013.042.00007 (Box 42)
    - September, 1975; UA001.013.042.00008 (Box 42)
    - September, 1975; UA001.013.042.00009 (Box 42)
    - October, 1975; UA001.013.042.00010 (Box 42)
    - October, 1975; UA001.013.042.00011 (Box 42)
    - October, 1975; UA001.013.042.00012 (Box 42)
    - October, 1975; UA001.013.042.00013 (Box 42)
    - November, 1975; UA001.013.042.00014 (Box 42)
    - November, 1975; UA001.013.042.00015 (Box 42)
    - November, 1975; UA001.013.042.00016 (Box 42)
    - November, 1975; UA001.013.042.00017 (Box 42)
    - November-December, 1975; UA001.013.042.00018 (Box 42)
    - December, 1975; UA001.013.042.00019 (Box 42)
    - December, 1975; UA001.013.042.00020 (Box 42)
    - December, 1975; UA001.013.042.00021 (Box 42)
    - December 1975, December 1976, 1975 -- 1976; UA001.013.042.00022 (Box 42)
    - January, 1976; UA001.013.042.00023 (Box 42)
    - January, 1976; UA001.013.042.00024 (Box 42)
    - January, 1976; UA001.013.042.00025 (Box 42)
    - January, 1976; UA001.013.042.00026 (Box 42)
    - January-March, 1976; UA001.013.042.00027 (Box 42)
    - February, 1976; UA001.013.042.00028 (Box 42)
    - February, 1976; UA001.013.042.00029 (Box 42)
    - February, 1976; UA001.013.042.00030 (Box 42)
    - February, 1976; UA001.013.042.00031 (Box 42)
    - February-March, 1976; UA001.013.042.00032 (Box 42)
    - March, 1976; UA001.013.042.00033 (Box 42)
    - March, 1976; UA001.013.042.00034 (Box 42)
    - March, 1976; UA001.013.042.00035 (Box 42)
    - April, 1976; UA001.013.042.00036 (Box 42)